<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
 * TapLock
 * Copyright (C) 2012 Bryan Emmanuel
 * 
 * This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 *  it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 *  the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 *  (at your option) any later version.
 *  
 *  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 *  but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 *  MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 *  GNU General Public License for more details.

 *  You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 *  along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 *  
 *  Bryan Emmanuel piusvelte@gmail.com
-->
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Tap Lock</string>
    <string name="button_add_device">Add device</string>
    <string name="chk_sec">Secure</string>
    <string name="btn_bt_scan">Scan for new Devices</string>
    <string name="msg_scanning">scanning&#8230;</string>
    <string name="no_devices">No saved devices</string>
    <string name="mn_remove">Remove device</string>
    <string name="widget_device_name">unknown</string>
    <string name="widget_device_state">toggle</string>
    <string name="ttl_enablebt">Bluetooth is required.</string>
    <string name="msg_enablebt">Enable bluetooth?</string>
    <string name="msg_device_not_conf">%s, not configured on this device.</string>
    <string name="button_about">About</string>
    <string name="about">Tap Lock uses NFC and Bluetooth to lock and unlock PCs.\u000A\u000ACurrently, Gnome Desktop on Linux is supported.\u000A\u000ASetup:\u000A\u000A1. Install Java 1.5\u002B on the PC\u000A2. Copy the TapLockServer.jar file to the PC using one of the \u0022Get the TapLockServer.jar\u0022 options.\u000A3. Configure the Tap Lock Server to start at login on the PC using these examples\u003A\u000A\u000Ajava -jar \u002Fhome\u002Fuser\u002FTapLockServer\u002FTapLockServer.jar \u003E\u002Fdev\u002Fnull 2\u003E\u00261\u000A\u000Ajava -jar C\u003A\u005CUsers\u005Cuser\u005CTapLockServer\u005CTapLockServer.jar\u000A\u000A4. Make sure that Bluetooth is enabled on the PC and that the Tap Lock Server is running\u000A5. In the Tap Lock app, on the Android device, press Add device to setup the PC\u000A6. After pairing with the PC, select that newly added device for further options.\u000A\u000ADevices can be toggled by launching a URI or URL from Tasker or NFC Task Launcher using the format taplock\u003A\u002F\u002Fdevicename\u000A\u000AOn Windows, you can run the following command, updated for the installation path, to start the Tap Lock Server at logon.\u000A\u000Aecho java -jar \u0025USERPROFILE\u0025\u005CTapLockServer\u005CTapLockServer.jar > \u0022\u0025USERPROFILE\u0025\u005CAppData\u005CRoaming\u005CMicrosoft\u005CWindows\u005CStart Menu\u005CPrograms\u005CStartup\u005CstartTapLockServer.bat\u0022</string>
    <string name="email_instructions">Configure the Tap Lock Server to start at login on the PC using these examples\u003A\u000A\u000Ajava -jar \u002Fhome\u002Fuser\u002FTapLockServer\u002FTapLockServer.jar \u003E\u002Fdev\u002Fnull 2\u003E\u00261\u000A\u000Ajava -jar C\u003A\u005CUsers\u005Cuser\u005CTapLockServer\u005CTapLockServer.jar\u000A\u000A4. Make sure that Bluetooth is enabled on the PC and that the Tap Lock Server is running\u000A5. In the Tap Lock app, on the Android device, press Add device to setup the PC\u000A6. After pairing with the PC, select that newly added device for further options.\u000A\u000ADevices can be toggled by launching a URI or URL from Tasker or NFC Task Launcher using the format taplock\u003A\u002F\u002Fdevicename\u000A\u000AOn Windows, you can run the following command, updated for the installation path, to start the Tap Lock Server at logon.\u000A\u000Aecho java -jar \u0025USERPROFILE\u0025\u005CTapLockServer\u005CTapLockServer.jar > \u0022\u0025USERPROFILE\u0025\u005CAppData\u005CRoaming\u005CMicrosoft\u005CWindows\u005CStart Menu\u005CPrograms\u005CStartup\u005CstartTapLockServer.bat\u0022</string>
    <string name="button_license">License</string>
    <string name="license">Tap Lock\u000A\u000ACopyright &#169; 2012 Bryan Emmanuel\u000A\u000AThis program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.\u000A\u000AThis program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.\u000A\u000AYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program.  If not, see \u003Chttp://www.gnu.org/licenses/\u003E.\u000A\u000ABryan Emmanuel piusvelte@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="title_toggle">Toggling device</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="info_noinfo">No info provided.</string>
    <string name="info_taplocksettings">First, setup the TapLockServer on a PC using the instructions in the menu option ABOUT. Next, add that PC as a device using the menu option ADD DEVICE.</string>
    <string name="info_newdevice">Long press on devices for additional options, including changing the passphrase.</string>
    <string name="button_getserver">Get the TapLockServer</string>
    <string name="msg_oops">Oops! Something went wrong, sorry!</string>
    <string name="msg_sdcardunavailable">The sdcard is not available. Is it inserted?</string>
    <string name="device_uri">taplock\u003A\u002F\u002F%s</string>
    <string name="msg_deviceexists">This device is already defined as %s.</string>
    <string name="msg_nodevices">No unpaired devices found. Are they visible?</string>

</resources>